Hi, this is Sean Hobson.
Right now we're talking about how to play good man-to-man defense and what your responsibilities are in the man-to-man defense.
First of all, we've seen that when the ball is at the man that you're assigned, then you're going to be in man-to-man, or "on the ball" defense.
So right now, his man has the ball, so Kyle is going to be on the ball in defense.
So go ahead and get in a good defensive stance.
Now, as the ball moves, his assignments are going to change.
One pass away, we know that he is now in deny.
What we want to focus on in this clip is something called "help side" defense.
If he is not on the ball and if he is not one pass away, he doesn't have to worry about that man passing the ball back, as the ball moves to the next guy, he no longer has to be concerned necessarily about what the ball is going to do with his man.
Instead, what he's going to do now is, he is going drop off to where he can look outside and he can see both his man and the ball.
And we want him to take his hands and point: man, ball.
And this way, when the ball skips back, he can quickly close to his man or if the ball goes back here, he could go back into deny.
But in this position, we call this "help side" defense.
Now he can help if this guy drives or he can help if the ball comes from the opposite wing.
So, we've got on the ball, we've got deny and now we've talked about help side defense.